Friends with beer!
Peter I need this beer more than you will ever know right now
I think you need that beer more than I need this beer and I could really use this beer
The technology rage is building inside of me. Technology can't even but we have established that on a previous no longer existent podcast
That's right. So let's talk about our beers. You go first because your beer was probably ready first.
I am going tonight.
Going tonight. Going to drink tonight. Good night. Going tonight a Golden Road Brewing
mango cart
mango wheat ale. That looks very good. I had this this past weekend and
was good enough that I looked it up and found it in a local store and
and bought a 15 pack.
You and I are definitely in the summer of fun mood because once again, I've got something
a little fruity.
I've got the Ex Novo.
Ex Novo.
It's called the Cactus Wins the Lottery and it is a I can't read that.
It's very dark in here.
Sour ale with prickly pear.
Excellent.
A fruity summery beer.
Oh, that sounds delicious.
Oh, I just got I'm gonna watch out, I'm gonna lick my pop filter here.
That's gross.
Okay.
Probably is.
If a man can't lick his pop filter, what can he lick?
I don't even.
Oh, are you asking me to stop?
Cheers everybody.
Cheers.
That first sip, right?
Let's yeah.
Ding.
Let's hope our day, your day at least gets better from here.
It will.
It already is.
So that was the most easily fixed of the technology problems that I've had lately.
Have you tried turning it off and on again?
I didn't actually turn it off, but I did reboot it.
Well functionally, that's pretty much the same.
What the hell happened?
So listener, what you don't know is that the call, the FaceTime call with Scott right now
just hung up as I'm saying this.
So I'm going to try calling him back and see what happens.
It's ringing.
That was interesting.
Still ringing on his side.
And now it says that Scott's FaceTime is unavailable.
I guess I'll just sip my beer.
Oh, now he's calling.
Oh, hi Scott.
back. You're still recording right? I'm still recording. I'm gonna have to edit
out some swear words. All of a sudden my... what happened to you? Did your light go out on
purpose? I think that my lady in the tube just heard me give a command which I did
not give. Alexa turn on third floor lights. My screen went black and I
thought oh my god I can't believe it because I've replaced the power supply
in this Mac and I haven't had any power off issues ever since and that was I
don't know what months ago a year ago whatever mm-hmm over a year ago now I
I guess and all of a sudden my screen went black and I lost my FaceTime call, but everything else was running
So I think I don't know for me the call just died and I figured that you either got
Frustrated and hung up or that you can hit by a meteor
Why not both if I get hit by a meteor Peter?
I am gonna be frustrated and I really frustrated up and you may hang up. Yes
Turn on lights
we were talking about our beers and I was talking about how I have a
mango cart beer which I had first this
thing was Saturday after a 10k run with my buddy Greg and
We both liked it. And so, you know, I immediately bought myself a 15-pack
So this is like the third or fourth fourth time. I think I've had this beer now wait, and it's really good earlier
or didn't you say a 10 pack?
And then it was a 12 pack and now it's 15 pack.
You keep increasing.
No, it was a 15 pack.
Okay.
And once again, I have Cactus Wins the Lottery,
Sour Ale with Prickly Pear by Ex Novo,
and it is a sour ale and it's quite good.
I like it.
Well, I'm glad that they didn't lie about that
'cause I would hate to like take a big swig
of what you thought was a sour ale
and find out it was a Belgian quad or something.
Yeah, no danger of that.
Ah.
So how are you?
So, I'm okay.
I'm all right.
I hope you're doing better than me, technologically speaking.
I mean, that's hit or miss, really.
You know, I took a meeting today,
took a meeting while out on the trail running,
so that was fun.
So you were heavy breathing into your meeting.
I didn't have anything to say the entire time.
Well, no, about 35 minutes into it,
they said some things that I had to say.
Wait, no, not accurate, not safe.
Oh, I thought they were like,
"Peter, what should our business strategy be?"
And he says,
make trillions when we could make billions? That's pretty, that sounds kind of like them, yeah.
No, it was more like, hey, you know what, the security team, we need, you know, you guys have
grown to a point where we need to have you on call because someone called me out specifically, said,
we had, you know, during this outage last week when like this entire hospital was offline,
Peter Nikolaidis was very helpful. So the chief health information officer for the hospital,
which is my largest engagement, said, "Yeah, we should have him on call pretty much effectively 24/7."
And I was just like, "Hahahaha, we need to talk more money."
[Clears throat]
Because they thought that I would just do this as part of my existing contract, and I was like, "Yeah, no."
But doesn't your boss have a say in this?
He said, "We'll talk about it."
To you or to them?
Us. And then he talked about it, and he said that he's planning on not doing anything and hoping that it just blows over.
Are these people that have the ability to tell him what to do?
Yeah.
And/or to pressure him into quitting and leaving the country?
Okay.
Oh yeah. But then I would just say, "Okay, well, my work is done here. Goodbye."
Yes. I've done everything I could, which apparently is nothing.
Yeah, pretty much. Quantum et demonstratum.
So not just technology, but you were having a little bit of a fit with technology before this,
too. Like yesterday.
Yesterday, yeah.
It had something to do with horses that they rode in on.
Every horse, I think, if I recall.
Every horse they rode in on.
Yeah. Well, who are you going to do to these horses and why?
I said them and every horse they rode in on.
Got it. Shouldn't our bleep sound be the sound of a can opening?
It should be and I will get one.
OK, just making sure.
Maybe we could record our own.
We could we can rehearse that a few times.
That's a good idea.
It may need many takes.
We maybe we should do that now.
Maybe we should go through your 15 pack trying to get the right sound.
Awesome.
So what was up? What was technology frustrating you last few days?
I have an external heart rate monitor for when I exercise
and it is a armband heart rate monitor.
wahoo tickr fit? wahoo tickr fit.
Same one I have.
That is correct. And it has been it's just more reliable.
Like I have an Apple Watch.
Apple Watch to me is something I can't have any downtime on for exercising.
But in terms of heart rate monitor, it's on your wrist.
It's very hard for an optical heart rate sensor to be accurate
when it's on your wrist. It's just not the best.
That said, let me interrupt you for just a quick second.
Back when I got my watch, my Apple Watch, it was rated as the most accurate
when it came for fitness tracking in its class.
In its class, that's right.
But that's the class of wrist based heart rate monitors.
Yeah. And it is very accurate for that. It's quite good.
It's just I wanted something a little more accurate.
And I bought the wahoo tickr fit.
And when I bought it, it was really reliable.
I got good results from it over time.
And I don't know why, but over time it has started to lowball me seriously.
I know when I'm doing 109 beats per minute
and when I'm doing 140 beats per minute, I can tell the difference.
Mm hmm. I did some math, by the way.
Let me see.
140 is greater than 109 if that's what you're wondering.
Yeah, but just in a workout that I did the other day, for example, the heart rate monitor,
the external heart rate monitor was giving me 6.6 calories per minute if you do the math.
And the Apple Watch one was calculating me out at 8.8 calories per minute.
That's based on heart rate.
Got it.
That's because of the difference in heart rate that it was measuring.
hour, that equates to external heart rate monitor would say,
okay, his heart rate was such that he's burned just under 400
calories, whereas the Apple watch would say, no, he's done
528 now extrapolate that to 90 minutes.
Yeah.
Pretty soon I'm putting in an extra half hour to 45 minutes
to get the same amount of calories burned.
Yep.
And it's frustrating.
And I don't want to do that.
I'm not exercising just for the fun of it.
I do longer work.
Like I don't just work out for 40 minutes or whatever.
I typically do an hour to 90 minutes, sometimes two hours.
Yeah, that's fine.
But if I'm going to do that, I want to know reliably
how many calories I'm actually burning.
Yeah, absolutely.
I don't know why.
I don't know if it was a software update.
I did see some things on Reddit.
People were saying the latest firmware update borked them as well.
All I know is I've decided that external optical sensor
heart rate monitors in me are not friends.
My Apple Watch, though, the last two days has been pretty good
and it's been giving me about what I think should be.
And but the whole reason I went away from it to begin with was I was getting just because of where it's positioned
I would get sweaty. Yep, the bank etc. You know, you know all the reasons why yeah
So now I've ordered a chest strap heart rate monitor and those are not optical, right?
Those use electrodes. Okay, and so I'm gonna see how that goes
I have been using the wahoo tickr fit since you told me about it and I love mines great
Mine used to be great too. But the reason I bought mine was as of watch OS 7
the Apple watch
Completely lost its ability to give me accurate heart rate for at least
Like 15 20 minutes of any running workout it would start out and I can always tell like those days when I have forgotten
To make sure that the ticker fit is paired with my watch
because I'll glance down at the workout and it shows like no heart rate and
on those days you look at it and you'll see the heart rate is showing at like
180 or 190 beats per minute, right? Right, which is not where I'm at
That's the problem with optical heart rate monitors and that is the problem in specific with the Apple watch
Adjusting the band can make a difference sliding it up and down the arm slightly can make a difference. Absolutely
That's what I was having with the Wahoo though where I would just barely adjust it and I would get a 20 or 30 beat per
Minute difference. Yep, and it's like which is real who knows pick one. So on that note now, here's the thing for me though
I've had an Apple watch series to a series 4 and it's now a series 6
Mm-hmm. I had the same problem with the 4 and the 6 when I'm watch OS 7 came out before
Completely lost its ability to get an accurate reading early on in my runs
Have you thought about not getting even numbered watches? Well, the seven should be coming out next month. So sure. Why not?
Let's try it. Yep
So I got the ticker fit and I love it now on that note a year and a half ago last March
I ran my first
13.2 miles
Not part of a race just a personal best longest run ever. Yeah this Sunday
I ran 13.25. So last year it was actually it was 13.21 and this year I ran 13.25 just on Sunday and
The times between those two were within like five seconds of each other
But the heart rate
Last year was shown as an average of 165 beats per minute
And this year it was like 135 beats per minute
Do you believe that 165? That seems awfully high.
165 is when I'm working pretty hard.
Yeah, that's hard work.
So now I'm starting to question those numbers.
Although, I will say this year it felt a lot easier than it did last year.
Oh, I'm sure you're more fit and I'm sure that you're more efficient.
And for the same exercise your heart rate's not going to be as high.
But running for 13 miles at 165 beats per minute? I don't...
It seems pretty stressed out. I would have been like, you know, like really working hard.
Yeah, right.
But that makes me wonder then, that means like basically I have years of heart rate data which is unreliable.
Maybe.
Yeah, I mean on that note, I need to move on to beer number two.
Oh.
Same one as last time. Yeah, a return appearance is Ithaca Brewing Company's Apricot Wheat.
So, I'm going from a mango wheat beer to an apricot wheat beer.
Now I remember this one. I like the flavor and the taste profile of this.
You almost said the taste prophylactic.
I heard you.
Prophylactic, exactly. No, I mean that taste prophylactic, that's like a beer that tastes so
garbage that you just don't even want to drink it. It keeps you away.
This one is not as sweet as the mango cart, but it's got a very, you know,
nice profound apricot flavor. So, cheers.
Cheers. I'm still on my first beer. I'm going to go get my second one,
which will be another one that I haven't had before.
Ah, I thought about that too. I actually did think about burning through because I had
seven new beers in my fridge. Most of them wheat beers and stuff and I thought it was like,
"Well, I could go through two. Thank you, you're catching up. Good job."
Yeah, I'm out.
But I decided I also have a lot of these apricot wheats here too,
so I should you know like burn through one of those. So that's what I'm doing. So...
So, yeah, I mean unquestionably I still love my Apple Watch but my friend,
so speaking about our issues with fitness trackers, I think this is like the fitness
tracker slam episode. So my buddy Greg runs with a Fitbit. I don't remember which model.
Let me ask him. What model Fitbit do you have? My dearest Gregory. My dearest Gregory,
may I make of you an inquiry? So we'll ask him what happened. It's not like the super duper top
of the line latest and greatest. I don't know what he runs, but he has been having issues with his
distances. Now he is training for the Bay State Marathon, which is literally, oh it's two months
away from today actually. So I have in the past volunteered to just run along with him as long
as it made sense. For now, again this this weekend, this coming Sunday, I think he's planning on
either 14 or 15 miles and stuff and his, you know, it goes up to about that. But it's mostly he's
He's doing like six miles, three miles, six miles, 15, six, three, six, 16, six, three, six, 14, whatever.
He's not doing too many multiple long days in a row. He's alternating.
Yeah. So I'll probably go with him all the way up to, but not including the marathon, so...
You should include the marathon.
Eh, eh, it's not really a... Eh, maybe, I don't know.
But anyway, so I'm sort of half-heartedly half-training for a marathon now,
which includes effectively a half marathon every week.
You've run more than one half marathon unsupported.
Like the only time I ever ran half marathon distance,
it was in a supported event.
So I could run by somebody
and grab a drink out of their hand or whatever.
Right, yeah.
So, you know, anyway, so that's, that's what's fun.
But he is also having trouble, you know, challenges.
Cause he uses, he's a Strava guy.
So he uses Strava.
Like me, he will often use footpath to plot a route.
I like Footpath 'cause it lets you plot out a route
and then send it to your Apple Watch
and it'll tell you, "Turn left here," and so.
And it's got better support for trails
than something like Google or Apple Maps.
Yes.
So he has his Fitbit
and he has been getting inconsistent results.
The GPS just fritzes out.
And I think that it seems to be just like basing
or estimating his distance based on step count.
Now that said, we were almost exactly 5K from my house
on our way back, just finishing like the last three miles.
And I told him, you know, no, this is gonna work out
just perfectly 'cause from this cemetery back to my house,
it's almost exactly, you know, 5K
'cause I've done this bunch of times.
We did that and we get back to, you know,
the final turn into my street that I live on
and I was still a quarter mile short.
Wow.
And so I'm like, so I don't know what's going on.
He's got the Fitbit Versa 3 right now.
Okay.
So, just for kicks, a friend of the show, Adam Bell, has the top-rated Fitbit for things
like CrossFit.
And Greg and my running coach, Charlie, has the top-of-the-line Garmin, made for people
who are going to be off the grid for five days in a row.
Right, right, right.
And need something that can do that.
Wait, is this Charlie guy the same guy who was your roommate for a while?
Yeah, that's the same.
The one who, by the way, you can find at run with Charlie dot
wait, Charlie, dot run, run with run with Charlie dot run, I believe.
Charlie with beer run.
Yeah. No, no.
We'll find that and put a link in the show.
I'm pretty sure it's run with Charlie dot run.
So it's like run with Charlie, run, run, Charlie, run.
By the way, listeners, I don't know Charlie very well, but I have seen Charlie.
And if you just by going by looks if you ever want to pick a running coach that guy is the running coach to pick
Indeed. Yes, if you're going by looks he looks like a runner code that dude looks freaking fit. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, so yes it is. It's it's run with Charlie run. Yep. That's it
I'm so definitely put a link into the show notes because everyone will forget that by now
Oh, he's she picked a new he picked a new theme for his website that's great
So anyway, Greg has been having trouble with his Fitbit. And so I told him dude, you got to get a new one, right?
And I was looking really quickly on Amazon and you know, then I've read some reviews like you know
I think was Tech Target. I read their best running fitness tracker watches for 2021
And I think Garmin was like the number one and then there was a new brand that neither of us had ever heard of
Coming in and like the number two had four slots and it was only like 200 bucks compared to the others
which were all like four or five and six hundred dollars.
What website was this?
This was I believe it was TechTarget.
So we can dig that up.
Apple watch came in the top ten but it was not you know it was it was like number nine
on the list as far as runners go.
But you know as much as a runner that I am I'm more than a runner and I do appreciate
the integration with my iOS devices and be able to make phone calls and stuff like that
from the watch.
Yeah right right right right.
see that changing for me anytime soon and plus for me I think the metrics are good enough.
So they are and honestly the Apple Watch is really good as in terms of like I said it's
my device that I can't do with any downtime on. Yeah if my Apple Watch craps out I'm going
and buying another one that day like it doesn't matter if I get any money for my old one it
doesn't matter if it gets repaired I don't care I'm going to get one that day. I remember
what it was like when mine died last year just at the start of COVID. Yeah and I was
without it for weeks because of the, you know, because of the pandemic. And I remember going
back to running with a phone for the first time in months and I hated it.
It sucks.
Now that said, I've been using a running belt by FlipBelt and that changes the game totally.
I almost forget that I'm carrying anything when I have it on me. So it's the next best thing. But
But I generally like on a day like today,
when I expect to take a call on a meeting,
I will bring the phone with me, right?
'Cause it's hard to dial into a WebEx meeting on a watch.
But on days when I just need to be able to like
take a phone call, if someone needs to call me,
then I just use the watch and I leave the phone.
And most days I don't even take water with me.
If I'm doing like more than 10 miles or it's really hot,
I'll bring water.
But most days it's just like me, my watch
and my running shoes and I'm good.
See, I... Yeah, I could probably do that. I don't know, I drink a lot of water.
So, you know how they have these flip belt Arc water...
I have one of those. My buddy Greg has the smaller 6 ounce ones. I have the 11 ounce Arc.
I've got a different belt and it's got bottles about the size of that smaller one.
Now, the thing that I don't like about mine, I don't know how the water bottles touch on this,
but on mine they have these little plastic holsters that go on the belt that they go into.
And it looks really stupid and I'm not really a fan of it.
But anyway, just doing that five mile run I did the other day outside for the first time in a long time doing an outside run, I took one of those little bottles with me and I drank the whole thing.
I just I drink a lot while I exercise. And I don't know if I even want to run five miles without water, honestly. Maybe I would, but I don't know.
I found back last year when I was running and especially like when I did that 13 miler, the first one, it was a crutch for me.
I was using it as an excuse to stop and take a sip of water or take a break or something.
Oh, I never stopped a drink. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, I would. Otherwise I'd like, you know, start waterboarding myself or something.
Well, these little bottles, they've got a cap that makes it easy to...
And plus you got to remember, I'm a cycler. You don't... You just keep going while you eat and
drink. And same with running. I'll just keep going. And those little bottles I have, they've got a nice
little cap. You just pull it up with your teeth, take a squirt and then push it right back down.
You're good to go. You never stop.
So, you know, that's one way to do it. But I found like most days I'm like,
I don't need water, you know, so I just leave it behind.
Do you hydrate like crazy beforehand?
I try. I'm still working on that because I don't like having to stop to relieve myself
of everything that I hydrated like crazy beforehand. But I find that if I need to
give myself at least half an hour after I pound some water before I leave the door.
Otherwise it all wants to come out as soon as I start running.
You know, it's weird. Running is different, but in general,
once I start exercising, my biological needs kind of go away.
However, one big difference between running and biking is the old,
uh, emergency stop in the woods syndrome,
but running definitely brings that out way more than biking does.
Well, you're shaking, you know what I'm talking about?
But this, the thing is like, there's an initial hump that you have to cross.
You know?
So that's it.
Maybe that's the whole point of warming up.
Maybe that's why you're supposed to do that.
But let me say, let me put it this way.
I've never suddenly felt like I had to poop while I was riding a bike, but I have definitely
had that issue when I've been running.
That's a thing.
And in the book, I Hate Running and So Can You, he talks about that on at least two or
maybe even three times in the book about the number of times you have to stop during a
run.
Yeah.
I was like, that should be something that you could plan for.
Yeah, I don't ever want to be running and hear this.
You pooped your pants!
That happens a lot to runners apparently.
So that's a thing. Hey, I remember watching, oh what was it? I can't remember where I saw this,
but this poor bastard who was running like a marathon,
and he just pooped all down his own leg and everything. I mean it was everywhere,
and he just was crying and I felt bad for the guy because that's horrible. That is just horrible.
Yeah, that is horrible.
That's not-
That's one of one of the advantages of trail running versus,
you know, running in the city.
Yeah. And if it's trail running, first of all, you're probably alone
and there's places to hide to poop.
But also, if for some reason you do poop down your leg,
you can just say you fell in the mud. Perfect.
And as long as they don't get too close, they won't know the difference.
Gross. I'm just saying that options there.
Oh, boy. So moving on.
Yeah, but I still.
Moving back back to you.
you talk to the listener about moving back whatever you're moving back to. I'm I got
to get my second beer, friend. Oh wow, I thought you already had. No, it's downstairs in the fridge.
Go get your beer. I'm waiting. All right. Well, listener, this is the part in the show where where
I deliberately talk to you alone as if Scott, you know, had like technical difficulties or something.
So, back to my beer. Once again, Apricot Wheat Beer from Ithaca Brewing Company. It is a wheat
Sweet ale with natural apricot flavor, just like it was last episode, so that hasn't changed.
Tastes just like it.
So it's nice.
It's not sweet.
It tastes ever so slightly...
Do I want to even say hoppier?
Let me see if that's the word.
No, not hoppier.
It's just less sweet than the mango cart, but not in a bad way.
if you want a really sweet beer, this is not the one that you would get. But no, it tastes
pretty good. And you know, I'm enjoying it because I am a wheat beer kind of guy. So
that's the kind of thing I like. So I would check it out. But if you are into a lighter,
fruitier, sweeter beer, I definitely recommend that you check out Golden Road Mango Cart.
On that note, I have a rogue. I have a rogue Newport Days D A Z E. It is a hazy pale ale.
My wife sampled this earlier today.
It is not an India pale ale.
Good.
And this looks like another light.
So we've been doing the light summery beers
and I kind of like that about this.
Well, it's because it's summery.
I agree.
It's light and summery.
It's funny you mentioned that too,
'cause Sam Adams this year,
their seasonals are Wicked Easy and Wicked Hazy.
And one of them is a summer IPA
and the other's a summer wheat beer.
So.
one's not too bad. I kind of like the other one better but they've got a
little star chart here. Can you see this? Yeah I see the star yes. And then
they highlight the part of it where so it's more tropical and more citrusy. It's
less malty, less bitter, less... what does that word say? Pine. No no pine. No pine
intended. So no pine intended. Do not pine. Yeah so I can taste a little bit of the
hops on this but it is citrusy. If I had to choose between these two beers, I would definitely
go for the Ex Novo Cactus Beer Sour Ale over this.
But Rogue is one of my... but I do... there
are a lot of good Rogue ones that I like and I think in the past I've had the Rogue Honey
Kolsch style ale on this podcast and that one's really good. This is pretty good. I
I don't think I would buy this over their honey coles style ale for sure.
Okay. Have you had their like rogue dead guy ale or anything like that?
I've had some of those, yeah. I'm not a big fan of those.
Got it.
All right, I was just curious.
Yeah. This is good though. I like it, but I definitely would buy the honey one first.
Excellent.
For any listeners out there.
So I was trying to find the same article on those fitness trackers that I mentioned and somehow I got redirected over to amazon.co.uk
Well, Tech Radar, I don't know what it is, but it ain't a fitness related website.
This is not Tech Radar, sorry.
Why did you switch me over?
You are shopping amazon.co.uk. I know, and that's the problem.
Yeah, that is the problem.
I want to go home.
Thank you for telling me that thing that I don't want to do that I'm currently doing
Technology can't even we're having quite a week
Technology and even you know what here's what's happening to us the right malware can corrupt the machines entire system
It won't even be able to start it would take decades for them to recode it. Whoa in tech in decades to recode it
Oh my god over two terabyte over two terabyte of decade
huh
That's hilarious. Can't make it up. Yeah, I never watched season two of Mr. Robot.
Season two was definitely different. At first I did not like it as much. When I went back and
watched some of it again, I realized that it actually was pretty good TV, but it's definitely
a different feel. And I can see why it lost some people. But overall, you've got to watch the whole
series. Right. There are some arguments to be made for the ending was disappointing, blah blah blah,
But overall, it was just a good ride.
A lot of violence, a lot of characters dying and unexpected in sad ways.
And cool. Yeah. Wait.
I really don't like that when a series I am.
I have to assume I could easily look this up, but I'm lazy.
And dear listener, you're paying absolutely zero dollars for this podcast.
So you're getting every cent of your investment back.
So like, I hate it when a series takes like a 90 degree turn
in the third or fourth or fifth season or in this case maybe the second season. Like
I remember so I did not finish the series but I watched the first several years of Vikings
which I don't remember was HBO or Showtime I think it was Showtime, I don't remember.
That's why I never heard of it then.
Yeah, I mean it was you know, it's like a fictional account of this you know, famous
Viking and stuff.
Guys with horns.
Those guys, yes, the ones with the horns. The horny guys from Iceland.
I think that's all the guys from Iceland.
Yeah, I'll tell my friend Jacob. I'm sure he'll agree.
Okay.
I watched the first few seasons. I was like, yeah, this is pretty good. I liked it.
And then they change things. They kill off the main character and they make it instead about his sons.
And I think what happened was then Amazon picked it up.
And like in one, like between seasons, I don't remember, six and seven or five and six or whatnot,
the first new episode opens up with the former main characters, now ex-wife,
and her wife, and they are training and doing jiu-jitsu.
Okay.
These are Vikings.
Right.
But like, well, you know what we need to do for the next season?
We need to make her a lesbian and make them practice jiu-jitsu.
Right.
And I was just like, oh, so this is where you guys jump the shark.
Got it.
It was like, and I just,
I think I may have finished out that season,
but I couldn't go on to the next one.
I was like, this is terrible, so.
Yeah, I would not say
that Mr. Robot took a hard left turn,
but I would say that it definitely has a different feel
the second season, but it's not out of line with the series
once you get through it and realize what's going on.
Yep.
It's not like this makes no sense.
It does make sense.
It's just that I think based on the first few episodes, some people thought,
oh, this entire thing is only going to be about hacking and it's just going to be about the leaked computer skills and blah, blah, blah.
And it's not. It's a lot more interesting than that.
But to be honest, OK, that's kind of what kept me going was that it wasn't just that because I'm good with that.
But I don't really want to watch a show that doesn't go any deeper than that.
Right. There was more to it.
Another one that comes to my mind when I think of shows that I initially liked and then took -
Umbridge at?
A hard right turn.
Oh, okay.
Was this is like more than 10 years ago, The Unit. It starred the guy I don't remember
his name but he does all the Allstate commercials and it was about a squad it was basically Delta
Force and you know, like the first episode started off and I was like "dude, this is like G.I. Joe,
this is awesome!" And you know like there's some terrorist here and so they send in this guy and he
you know taps two Rangers and they like air drop in and you know save the day and whatnot.
And I watched the first couple of seasons I was like "Yeah this is really cool!" And then
I think it was like the fourth season or something they introduced Robert Patrick
aka Terminator 2. Oh okay. As like their new commanding officer but where they lost me was
they decided like, "Well, you know what we, what, you know, Command has decided we have to do is,
we need to include your wives on your missions now." On the missions? Yeah. So, like, they would
be doing these undercover things and all of a sudden their wives are now just put into the
missions just part of it, just like that, with like no training or anything. Well, I was going
to say, I have zero issue and in fact would welcome them having women involved as well,
but those would be people that had trained.
Those would not just be your wife. If you're a Delta Force highly trained operative,
doesn't mean that suddenly your wife is too. That's not how it works.
That is not how it works.
I mean, G.I. Joe, they had a couple of strong female figures.
There were, I can think of at least four. That's like one percent of the whole thing.
But I just noticed when I was looking at the cast and crew, by the way, whatever happened to IMDB,
It is a horrible website now. But anyway, Amazon bought it.
Wes Chatham is in that. He is in The Expanse, and I really like The Expanse.
Oh, okay. I watched the first... I want to say first episode of The Expanse and could not get into it.
Oh, yeah, I've heard that before, but it gets pretty good.
I've heard that too.
And they get more nuanced with some of the characters, yeah.
Like, his character in particular, he's a bit of a psychopath who just goes around killing anybody that he deems needs killed,
but there's actually more to him than that and they kind of get into it.
They get into why he's that way.
They get into him changing a little bit over time, becoming more of a normal person.
But it's pretty good.
I'm not going to say it's a perfect show, but it's definitely an enjoyable show.
I mean, let's be honest. Haven't we all had days like that?
We have definitely all had days where we felt like, you know what?
I've got to kill some people that need to be killed.
And by the way, that's pretty much all of them.
There you go. What else do we have?
We're getting pretty close.
I was going to talk a little bit about Windows 365.
Okay, let's hear about it because I don't know anything about it.
Though I use Windows every day at work, I don't have any...
Windows is one of those who cares operating.
There's nothing exciting about it.
It says a guy who, you know, is always on a Mac,
but for 90% of the rest of the world.
But I mean, it's a who cares thing.
It's not for people that really give a shit about their computing experience.
I would argue.
Okay.
It's not made for the computing experience.
It's made to be a computer operating system.
It fulfills that duty.
But I also am not mad at it.
Like I don't, it doesn't enrage me
that I have to use Windows, for example.
It's fine.
I'll use it at work.
It has its uses.
We use a lot of Windows Server for different things.
We use a lot of Windows Server for systems
that have to talk to each other
and they need tons of multiple incoming
or outgoing connections.
And so for that, we use Windows Server.
And the reason why we use Windows Server
instead of some Unix or Linux variant for that kind of thing
is just because it's easier to find C# programmers apparently
than it is to find people who, you know, the web would argue otherwise.
But for applications like ours, apparently that's the case.
Yep. Well, the thing with Windows 365 is essentially it is Windows in the cloud.
So it's Microsoft hosting a virtual desktop infrastructure for you.
OK. That's what it is.
It's not going to replace desktop windows, correct?
Well, it could, but you still need something.
you need some sort of device to use as the remote desktop client to get to this thing in the cloud.
Right, but what I mean is Microsoft isn't going to say, "Everyone's going to use this model.
No one's going to have Windows running locally on their PC."
No, no, no. But as more and more places move to virtual desktop infrastructure,
because it's more secure, it's more easily backed up and restored, etc.
Right, and somebody logs in and they get their profile.
I mean, it's...
Exactly.
But what I was thinking is like when, knock on wood,
when this seven year old Intel Core i5 desktop of mine
finally kicks the bucket and I've got a Macintosh again,
I'll probably just replace it with a Windows virtual
desktop in the cloud, either Windows 365
or maybe I'll use the Amazon offering.
Sure.
But I can see myself not needing
a physical Windows device anymore.
That'd be nice.
Which is kind of liberating.
You know, because literally I could use it from a tablet.
You could, I mean, it's not a pleasant experience,
but you can do it with a phone.
Yeah, I wouldn't.
I, yeah.
Tablet, another, you know, Mac, whatever, web browser.
So, and that's kind of nice though.
Like, you know, being able to like always have access,
anywhere you have internet access,
you have access to quote unquote, your computer.
Yeah.
You know, so that is pretty cool.
It's like a better RDC experience.
Uh huh.
Nice. I'm almost done.
On that note, I just finished mine.
I'll wait for you to catch up.
What else what else do we got?
I think we went through everything I wanted to cover.
Oh, I didn't talk about yoga and meditation but we can save that till the next episode.
Well okay.
My coworker just sent me a picture of the inside of our toolbox and there's a screwdriver
in there and it is a Phillips screwdriver and it is severely bent and he says "by the
way, what kind of people work here anymore?"
Apparently he's not pleased with the bent screwdriver.
I mean it was used as a pry bar.
It's pretty obvious.
Apparently people can't even.
On that note, I think we should call this a day.
Oh, one thing I still have, I haven't listened yet to that beer size that we did the other
time that's like 10 or 15 minutes long.
It may or may not be released.
I don't know.
I'll have to, oh, well I was going to say I'll go back and give it a listen, but apparently
I can't. No, not right now. It's never been released. Well on that note, Scott, if, excuse
me, if I have to burp, what do I do? Okay. If people want to get in touch with us, what
do they do? Well, they go to friendswithbeer.com or they can tweet at us at friendswbeerpod.
Should I use the alias? Why is that so funny? Should I use the alias? I don't know. It just
is friends w-beer pod friends w-beer pod should i use that no one will ever use that
but if you want to please do we want your feedback and i think there's beer dot tweetback dot us that
will also lead you to friends w-beer pod us okay friends will be your pod i like that so great
Great. Excellent. And we do want listeners to talk to us. We do. We like feedback, even if it's just
something silly. You know, if you try one of the beers that we have, you know, tell us what beers
you think we should try. And if they're IPAs, no, but you can still tell us. That's right. If they're
IPAs, we'll pretend like we never got your message. Yeah. So I don't know what happened to that email.
It did just out in the void somewhere. Well, we never gave them an email address, so it definitely
will be an email.
So, where else can people find you, Scott, on the interwebs?
What else are you up to these days?
Well, I am part of bubblesort.show, so you can go there.
I'm crouching inside that website just waiting for someone to contact me.
BubbleSort also has a bubble sort slack, all the links are on the website and I have a
website called scottwillsey.com and occasionally I post stuff.
I've been posting a series of how I use drafts for publishing blog posts from my iPad Pro
using a combination of drafts, actions, and shortcuts.
And I think I have an SSH series I need to finish.
I don't know.
I just publish stuff.
I just remembered we had talked about having you come on to blurring the lines and telling
Adam how to use his iPad.
Does he really want that?
He does.
Oh, okay.
I think he does.
Like more than I do for sure.
Right.
No, he was, I said that on a recent episode though too.
So yeah, I think he might actually like look at that and like, well, I never thought about
using it like that before.
So he doesn't, that's, I don't, he's from Tennessee, man.
He sounds like that.
Trust me.
Not exactly like that.
I've had two beers.
Give me some credit.
This is what you've never heard him after he's had a few beers.
Maybe that's exactly what he sounds.
That is true. But you've got to remember, I've been podcasting with Vic a lot.
Vic is from Kentucky and he will out accent Adam any day.
Yeah. Well, on that note, I think we should, as we would say on the Blurring
the Lines podcast, we should probably push the big red button.
Tell your friends.